<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tooros</string>
    <string name="policy">THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS AN ELECTRONIC RECORD IN THE FORM OF AN ELECTRONIC CONTRACT FORMED UNDER THE INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ACT, 2000 AND THE RULES MADE THEREUNDER AND THE AMENDED PROVISIONS PERTAINING TO ELECTRONIC DOCUMENTS / RECORDS IN VARIOUS STATUTES AS AMENDED BY THE INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ACT, 2000. THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT REQUIRE ANY PHYSICAL, ELECTRONIC OR DIGITAL SIGNATURE.\n\n THE TERMS “WE/US/OUR/TOOROS” INDIVIDUALLY AND COLLECTIVELY REFER TO TOOROS TECHNOLOGIES PRIVATE LIMITED AND THE TERMS “YOU/YOUR/YOURSELF” REFER TO THE USERS/MEMBERS UNDER MEMBERHSIP AGREEMENT. \n\n THIS PRIVACY POLICY IS A LEGALLY BINDING DOCUMENT BETWEEN YOU AND TOOROS (BOTH TERMS DEFINED ABOVE).\n\n THIS DOCUMENT IS PUBLISHED AND SHALL BE CONSTRUED IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE PROVISIONS OF THE INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (REASONABLE SECURITY PRACTICES AND PROCEDURES AND SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA OF INFORMATION) RULES, 2011 UNDER INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ACT, 2000; THAT REQUIRE PUBLISHING OF THE PRIVACY POLICY FOR COLLECTION, USE, STORAGE AND TRANSFER OF SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA OR INFORMATION.PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU INDICATE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND, AGREE AND CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE. YOU HEREBY PROVIDE YOUR UNCONDITIONAL  IRREVOCALBLE CONSENT TO TOOROS FOR THE PURPOSES PRESCRIBED UNDER INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO PROVISIONS OF SECTIONS 43A, 72 AND SECTION 72A OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ACT, 2000.\n\n
This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) sets out how Tooros collects, uses, protects shares any information that you give to us, when you use this website i.e. www.Tooros.in including its m-application (the “Website”). Tooros is committed to ensure that your privacy is protected to all possible, reasonable and commercial extent, as your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. Because we gather certain types of information about You in order to provide, protect, maintain and improve our services, We feel You should fully understand the Policy surrounding the capture and use of that information and solicit Your full attention towards it.\n\n By providing us your Information or by making use of the facilities provided by the Website, You hereby consent to the collection, storage, processing and transfer of any or all of Your Personal Information and Non Personal Information by Tooros, as specified under this Policy. You further represent and warrant that such collection, use, storage and transfer of Your Information shall not cause any loss or wrongful gain to you or any other person.\n\n
This Policy is a legally binding contract between You and Tooros, whose Website, You use or access or You otherwise deal with. This Policy shall be read together with the other terms and condition of the Website viz, Membership Agreement and Fees Policy being displayed on the website www.tooros.in   \n\n
Collection, Storage and Use of Personal Information:/n
When You apply for or maintain an account with Tooros, We collect certain personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”), such as: Your name, age, gender, photograph, contact preferences telephone number, mailing address, including but not limited to permanent and current residential addresses, e-mail address, financial information, internet protocol address, history of Your transactions ( booking and payment history), any other items of sensitive personal data or information, as such term is defined under the Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practices And Procedures And Sensitive Personal Data Of Information) Rules, 2011 enacted under the Information Technology Act, 2000, identification code of Your communication device which You use to access the Website, any other information that You provide during Your registration, use of availing of services via Website and other relevant documents viz; driving license and additional address cum identity proofs, as prescribed under the Membership Agreement of Tooros.By providing information to create a user account or complete Your user profile, You expressly and voluntarily accept this Policy and You shall be deemed to have voluntarily consented to authenticate Yourself with a government issued photo identity document which also contains your address, other than driver’s licence, (hereafter “Government-issued ID”) and hereby give Your voluntary consent for seeding identification details as provided in Government-issued ID to all Membership requirements and to provide Your identity information for authentication for the purpose of availing of the Services and to enforce any breach committed by you of the Memberships Agreement through police, government/enforcement authority or court of law.\n\n
In pursuit of excellence in the services offered few other personal information that We collect includes the following:\n
Vehicle Use Data: Vehicles will contain hardware that gathers and transmits information about vehicle use. This is done as a security measure against accident or theft and also to provide You with valuable services and information, such as other drivers’ data.\n\n
Location Tracking: To prevent theft, and to allow us to locate You in case of emergency, accident, lock-out, etc., We track the location of your vehicle. Your location information will be confined to Tooros service, and we endeavour not to make your location or movements’ public unless it is required under personal, medical and legal (recovery and insurance) exigencies. As part of our service, the location of your vehicle may be released to insurance companies, the police, courts, tribunals or similar law enforcement agencies, in the course of an investigation and/or accident claim, and to provide assistance in emergencies. Information regarding the location of each vehicle on Tooros Website is also transmitted to Tooros. .\n\n
Driver and vehicle Information: As a member of Tooros Website, you authorize us to access Your driver’s record, vehicle travelled history report pertaining to Your ride/trip from all applicable entities and authorities’. Moreover, You authorize all DMVs, RMVs, auto mechanics and all other entities and interested parties to release information to us regarding Your driving record and vehicle travel history. \n\n
You have the right to request to Tooros to discontinue the use of Your personal information. To withdraw Your consent to our collection and processing of Your information in future, You may do so by closing your account. \n\n
Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information:\n
We also collect non-personal information – data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual, including browser You use, usage details and identifying technologies. We may use, transfer, collect and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. If We do combine non-personal information with personal information, the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined. \n\n
Aggregate Information: We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as referring/exit pages, anonymous usage data, and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain Tooros services. \n\n
Third-party ad servers or ad networks may serve advertisements on the Website. These third-party ad servers or ad networks may automatically receive Your internet protocol address, when they serve ads to Your Internet browser. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Tooros to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that You fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. Tooros Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. \n\n
Cookies:\n
We use various technologies, including “cookies”, to collect non-identifiable information. A cookie is a piece of data that any website can send to Your browser, which may then be stored on Your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies Your computer but not You. To enhance Our Service, some Tooros pages use cookies, sent by Tooros or its third party vendors, or other technologies. You may control the effect of cookies through Your browser settings, however some features of Tooros Service may not work properly if Your use of cookies is disabled. \n\n
We may also use Web beacon or other technologies, often in conjunction with cookies, to enhance Our Service on a number of pages of Tooros Website. A non-identifiable notice of a visitor’s visit to a page on Tooros site is generated and recorded, and which may be processed by us or by Our suppliers. To disable some of these features, You may disable cookies in Your web browser’s settings. Web beacon and other technologies will still detect visits to these pages, but the notices they generate are disregarded and cannot be associated with other non-identifiable cookie information. \n\n
Information Sharing:\n
1. Tooros only shares Personal Information with third parties in the following limited circumstances: \n\n
•	To provide other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on Our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.\n
•	We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request including to law enforcement and in response to a court order, (b) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, technical or security issues, (c) enforce applicable terms and conditions of the Website including but not limited to Membership Agreement, Privacy Policy and Fees Policy, which may be further extended to investigation of potential violations thereof, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, safety or property of Tooros, its Users or the public as required or permitted by law.\n
2. To protect and recover Tooros assets viz; vehicles/ outstanding.\n
•	To protect Ourselves against third-party claims.\n
•	We reserve the right to transfer any/all personal information We have about You in the event that We sell or transfer all or a portion of Our business or assets.\n
•	We partner with outside companies to provide You with additional services related to Tooros, such as ride-sharing, referral programmes or parking benefits. When You purchase, register, or otherwise express interest in a product or service offered by a third party through Tooros or sponsored on Our Website, You consent to Our sharing your personal information with those parties. Participation in rewards programs, discount offers, contests, or other programs that involve third parties, authorizes Tooros to share Your personal information with those parties. A third party’s use of Your information is bound by contracts and agreements between Tooros and the third party. We only share information reasonably needed to provide additional services, and such shared information may be bound by other privacy arrangements. By sharing this information, You agree that Tooros is not liable or responsible for the actions or inactions of third parties.\n\n\n
Tooros may transfer/disclose/share information to those parties who support Our business, such as providing technical infrastructure services, analysing how Our services are used, measuring the effectiveness of advertisements, providing customer / buyer services, facilitating payments, or conducting academic research and surveys. \n\n
</string>
    <string name="objective">We have a dream to become one of the finest Self-drive Car rental service provider in Bhubaneswar. We believe that we will achieve this soon by making our clients happy every day.</string>
    <string name="company">Tooros Technologies is one the best Self-drive car rental company in Bhubaneswar with an innovative way of satisfying the requirement of the car rental industry. It was finally successfully launched by two entrepreneurs who are always interested by cars. If you love to travel then ToorosSelf drive car services will surely enable you to take control of the wheels and create memorable stories on your travel journey. With tooros, you can drive your dream car to your favorite destination at an affordable budget. Our wide range of cars includes Hatchbacks, Sedans SUV. We promise to deliver you completely Sanitized and well-maintained cars for self-drive car rent in Bhubaneswar. Apart from this we also have a dedicated team of customers supports executives who are available for you 24*7/365 days.\n\nBest things in life do not come with any usage caps, thus providing unlimited kilometers on every booking is our way of saying it to consumers. With Tooros self-drive cars, you drive happiness; you always have the dual advantage of freedom  privacy that makes us the best choice.\n\nSo, what are you waiting for? Time to book and ride!</string>
    <string name="cancel">•	Booking time to 72 Hours before start of the trip  25% cancellation of the amount.\n\n•
        72 hours to 24 Hours before start of the trip – 50% cancellation of the amount\n\n•
        24 hours or less before start of the trip – 100% cancellation of the amount. NO REFUND made for such cancellations.\n\n•
        If any booking is cancelled by Tooros due to non availability of vehicle for whatever reason, a full refund will be
        initiated. The refunded amount will reflect in the customers account within 7 10 working days.\n\n•
        Tooros reserve all rights to cancel booking with or without prior intimation.</string>

</resources>
